What do you mean, what is GitHub?
It's the largest, most complete development platform in the world.
Millions of developers use it, and it's not just developers.
These days, every company is a software company.
I thought you might say that.
Come on, let me show you.
It's an enterprise-transforming, start-up launching,
community-driven, super-secure, open-source championing,
cloud-based platform.
It's where the world builds software.
We created algorithms.
And global businesses.
We even want some Mars.
Or at least our code dead.
Oh, yes.
With GitHub, anything is possible.
But how?
Say this is Sonal, a senior software engineer.
And this is a team's project on GitHub.
Sonal and a team can create their own branches of code
to work together in parallel.
This is my branch, an alternate timeline
where I can build squash bugs and safely experiment.
There are communication and task delegation
tools right next to my code.
So when we're ready to merge, we merge instantly.
It works with thousands of branches
for over a million projects.
And with built-in project planning, automation,
CI-CD, and AI-enhanced code editing at every step.
You can move fast and get your ducks in a row.
But we've got to be safe about it.
GitHub has advanced security of automatic vulnerability
detection, secret scanning, and more.
So we can build and ship safely and securely.
So now you know what GitHub is.
You might wonder who GitHub is.
It's a student learning to code.
It's disruptors revolutionizing music.
It's a CEO transforming a global company.
It's 21,000 strangers working together
to take the first picture of a black hole.
It's a place for anyone from any way to build anything.
Anything you think the world needs.
What's that?
You already knew that?
Why didn't you say anything?
I was talking for ages back there.
It's embarrassing.